baby I Like It Raw raw Vantage likes it
raw baby I Like It Raw yeah baby I like
it
ra guess what everyone this is Chris
kennel from the raw advantage.com I'm
back here at Dr Sam's or treat and I got
a really good treat for you guys at
least a little bit of a tease sorry but
I'll be coming through with it I got a
lot of books coming out doing a lot of
fun videos and recipe hints and stuff
like that but with all concern over
sushi sheets Nori and being vegan as
well as Fukushima and pollution the
ocean and concern over that I developed
a seaweed free sushi roll that I think
is pretty damn fantastic what do you
ladies think about this we got nley
Ashley how are you doing great got melan
Lotus how you doing yeah so what what do
we have here is this one of my Sushi
this is one of your sushi dipped in your
famous sauce here it is from the other
side there we go look at that so it even
looks like Nori but actually I think it
tastes better what do you guys think
it's better than nor like I prefer this
over Nori yeah it's pretty damn
Delicious what do you think of the
dipping sauce beautiful beautiful so the
dipping sauce doesn't look yeah it's got
a bit of a ginger kicking to it I'll
give you a hint it's got some celery
juice in it got some sundried Tomatoes
teeny bit of radish and
uh little bit of black sesame
seeds o
dipping let's see it's a big bik you're
com from is a big
Bates it's so good so there we have it
let's look what's going over here hey
Miss Josephine Farm of Life H how you
doing are you bragging about these I'm
bragging a little what do you think are
they brag I brag yeah you like to brag
absolutely do you like them better than
nor I did you did look at that that was
genuine I can tell it's genuine look at
look at this we have all these beautiful
suit you over to my table to compliment
you on a and now can you please tell me
these are the these ones right here so
those are the ones with my rolls these
are all Nori rolls here going to look at
this whole spread look at this so this
is the first dinner here look at the
whole
crew here we go salad salad dressings
lots of
sushi there we are there we have it from
uh the farm of Life Brian calie you like
the recipe it's really good man uh that
that roll that special roll you made was
way better than a Nori roll really did
you you outdid yourself this time here
we go Caesar likes it
look well there you have it I guess uh
I'm going to have to share that recipe
with you pretty soon but let me know
below if you want to see that you know
it's going to be an upcoming book and
maybe I can divulge some Secrets here
you know got a lot so let me know hope
you guys love it signing out from Dr
Sam's Retreat Farm of
Life Dr Sam brother how you doing my
friend awesome got to be having you on
the retreat buddy a bless you man master
master at his craft yoga and chefing and
spiritual counseling but I am always
blessed to have TK on the retreat is he
just brings a whole to a whole another
level these are epic have you tried it
out H yes I have you did oh what what do
you think you like him as much as Nori I
I do like him a lot yeah Chris recreated
Nori without it being you know from the
ocean and it's all land all land stuff
but you when you taste it be pretty
Blown Away for sure stoked man thanks
always love to be your treats brother
raw habilitation next year we're going
to have Retreats back to back back to
back come to both to one the other we'll
both be there this be awesome love it
what do you think Melanie the girls
filled them without the filling it's
just a sheet so yeah the girls did fill
them you guys rule it oh so what do you
guys think of the Nori over here what's
going on Amazing yeah amazing oh I mean
what about my Nori this this no I was
talking about your Nori
they were better than the nor rolls a
yeah than the seaweed ones what do you
think I thought sweeter for the the real
deal the real nor I'm not a huge fan of
seaweed but yours are out of this world
love sign up right now and you can just
buy the book in the future I'm just
joking I'll give you the recipe in a
little bit rules are like the texture is
super good and it's time of sweet are
awesome thanks Kelsey much love guys to
more week you'll see you'll see some
more bits from the retreat
here secret
recipe it's better than
[Music]
Nori o check out these two super popular
videos tons of other recipe videos and
get your free ebooks by simply clicking
below L
recipes excited to announce my new
iPhone app free with 101 fre and rwome
recipes ter Retreat treats food
combining charts shopping carts and more